getthejob.com 2018-10-17

# Get The Job

### GetTheJob Privacy Policy

Effective Date: October 23, 2009. 

This privacy statement (this "Policy") covers the website http://www.getthejob.com (the "Site") and is applicable to all information about you ("you") collected through the Site ("User Information"). 

In this Policy, Avenue100 Media Solutions Inc., the owner of the Site, ("Avenue100," "we," "us," or "our") describes the types of information that Avenue100 gathers from you and the other people who visit the Site (the "Users") and how we may use that User Information. By providing any information, you agree to our use of that information consistent with this Policy. Please read this Policy carefully before providing us with any User Information. 

### Personally Identifiable User Information

Avenue100 may require that you register and provide us with various types of personally identifiable User Information through the Site. For example, you may choose to provide us your personally identifiable User Information, including, but not limited to, your name, mailing address, cell phone number and email address. We may store a cookie file on your hard drive so that our systems will recognize you each time you visit the Site. In that way, we can save your preferences from visit to visit and present you with a customized version of the Site without requiring you to log into the Site every time you visit. We may store your personally identifiable information in our systems for use in other ways as described in this Policy. 

In order for you to take full advantage of the Site, we encourage you to provide your personally identifiable User Information to us. Providing your personally identifiable User Information is, however, voluntary. You may choose not to provide us with your personally identifiable User Information by simply not entering it on the Site. While you will still have access to the Site even if you do not provide us with your personally identifiable User Information, you should understand that you will not be able to use certain services or features available through the Site that require you to enter your personally identifiable User Information in order to function. For example, we offer a service that sends an automated text message to your cell phone when a job comes through that matches you profile so that you can act swiftly. If you don't provide us with your cell phone number, you will not have the advantage of the speedy notice. 

If you do not register, then the User Information we collect from you is limited. For example, we log your IP address in order to help us to diagnose problems with our server, administer the Site and track usage statistics. Your IP address may vary each time you visit, or it may be the same, depending on whether you access the Site through an always-on type of Internet connection (such as cable or DSL), or through a dial-up connection. Either way, it would be very difficult for us to personally identify you through your IP address. If you reached the Site by clicking on a link or ad from another web site, then we may also log that User Information. This helps us to maximize our Internet exposure and to understand the interests of our Users. All of this User Information is collected and used only in aggregated form; that is, it is entered into our database, where we can use it to generate overall anonymous reports on our Users. 

### Cookies

We may place a small file known as a "cookie" on your computer's hard drive. A cookie may contain information that allows us to track your path through the Site and to determine whether you have visited us before. The cookie itself never contains your personally identifiable User Information. However, if you provide us with personally identifiable User Information, the cookie may allow us to personally identify you if you return to the site again. Our cookies cannot be used to read data from your hard drive and cannot retrieve information from any other cookies created by other websites. We use cookies in this manner to help us understand how Users use the Site, and to help us to improve the Site. From time to time, we may place cookies in connection with third party advertisements. You may refuse to accept a cookie from us by following the procedures for rejecting cookies specific to your web browser. Although you may do so, you may find that your browser reacts strangely when visiting not only the Site, but other web sites as well. 

We, or a data provider we have engaged, may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized ads, content or services. No personally identifiable information is on, or is connected to these cookies. The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to the registration data you have submitted to us, e.g., your email address, in hashed, non-human readable form. To opt-out of these cookies, please go to <http://www.privacychoice.org/companies> or <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>. 

### Clear Gifs

We also employ a software technology called "clear gifs," which helps us better manage content on the Site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with unique identifiers, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on web sites and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the User Information gathered by clear gifs to Users' personally identifiable User Information. Clear gifs may also be used by our third party advertisers. 

In addition to the User Information that you provide to Us or that We obtain about you from your use of our Site, We may also augment the data We have collected with other aggregate information from other online or offline sources. 

If you visit this Site by "clicking through" from another web site, and you have registered with that other web site, then certain information about you that you provided to that other website, such as the terms you were searching on that led you to the Site, may be transmitted to us and we may use it. You should review the privacy policy of any web site from which you reached the Site in order to determine what information was collected by that web site and for what purpose(s) you agreed that web site could use that information. We may or may not retain that information; if we do, then we will only use it in accordance with this Policy. 

### Avenue100 Policy Regarding Children Under the Age of 13

The Site is not intended for children under the age of 13, and Avenue100 does not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable User Information from children under the age of 13. 

### How We Use The User Information We Collect

User Information collected from you helps both of us. Either third party providers or us may use the User Information we collect to: 

  * Make your next visit to the Site more personalized 
  * Contact you regarding administrative issues such as questions about your specific request 
  * Send text messages to your cell phone about jobs that match your profile 
  * Compile anonymous statistical information for analysis 
  * Provide aggregated anonymous information to third parties 
  * Make telephone calls to you with information and offers 
  * Mail information and offers to you 
  * Email information and offers to you 
  * Present relevant information 

We will not share your cell phone number with third parties or use the number except to send you job alerts. 

### Consent to the Use of Third Party Providers

Please understand that Avenue100 may contract with other third parties to provide various services to Avenue100 relating to the Site on an outsourced basis rather than performing the services ourselves. For example, we may contract with an email provider to handle the distribution of email messages to Users of the Site. Likewise, we may contract with a web site hosting provider to host the Site for us. By visiting the Site, all Users consent to Avenue100 providing all User Information (whether or not personally identifiable) received or collected from those Users to such third party providers for the purpose of enabling the third party provider to provide these outsourced services to us. On an occasion we may use certain directory information that we have collected to send you information about products and services, or updates and other information we think may be of interest to you. We may permit a third-party to use non-personally identifiable information about your visit to our site in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you through the use of cookies, web beacons, clear GIF, pixel tags web bugs, action tags, or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. 

In addition, all Users consent to the collection, maintenance, and processing of their User Information (whether or not personally identifiable) by Avenue100 and these third party providers. Third parties will protect your information as Avenue100 would under the terms of this policy. 

### Opting Out

This privacy statement describes Avenue100's potential uses of your information. If you do not agree to our potential uses of your personally identifiable information as we have described for you, you are not required to provide that information to us. In addition, you may opt out of receiving advertising and promotional emails from us simply by responding to the opt-out email link provided on all email communications from Avenue100. You are not able to opt out of receiving administrative emails from us. 

You also may cancel or correct your personal information at any time. You can do this by e-mailing us at myinfo@getthejob.com with your User Name and the notice "My User Information" in the subject field of the e-mail. We will send you an e-mail to confirm your request. After we receive confirmation from you, we will correct or remove your information from the active database, but some information may remain in our archives. 

### Surveys & Contests

From time to time our Site may request information from Users via emailed surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the User therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose personally identifiable User Information. The requested User Information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact User Information will be shared with the contest or survey sponsors to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey User Information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of the Site. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests, these intermediaries will not use the Users' personally identifiable User Information for any secondary purposes. You may opt out of receiving emailed surveys or contests from us simply by responding to the opt-out email link provided on all email communications from us. 

### Third-Party Web Beacons

We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo! [click here.](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/opt_out/targeting/)

### Other Web Sites; Links

Please be aware that Avenue100's affiliates, promotional partners, advertisers, sponsors, and other third-party web sites accessible through the Site may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. Avenue100 is not responsible for any actions, content of web sites or privacy policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing personally identifiable information through linked web sites. 

### Disclosure of Your User Information

As you might expect, Avenue100 must cooperate with legal authorities, and may in some circumstances be required to disclose User Information (including personally identifiable User Information) in response to requests from law enforcement authorities, or in response to a subpoena or other legal process. We don't expect this to happen, but if it does, we will provide only the User Information required. We can also turn over User Information about you if we believe we must in order to prevent a violation of the law, and by accepting this Policy, you consent to our right to do so, in our sole discretion. You also consent to our disclosing User Information about you in the course of legal proceedings if we believe we are legally required to do so, if we reasonably believe that doing so may mitigate our liability, or if doing so will assist us in enforcing our legal rights. 

At some point, Avenue100 may establish subsidiaries or other related companies, or merge with or be acquired by another company. When that happens, then we may disclose to them your User Information, in which case we will request them to abide by this Policy. We may also disclose some User Information to a potential acquirer, although such disclosure would be subject to normal and customary requirements. If and when such a merger or acquisition takes place, we will notify you by publishing a public announcement on our Site. 

Of course, Avenue100 will take reasonable measures to secure the User Information Users provide to us, using industry-standard methods. All User Information is protected by password and accessible only to authorized Avenue100 personnel. However, there is a remote possibility that Internet transmissions containing a User's personally identifiable User Information may be intercepted by others. There is no way for us to ensure the privacy of User Information before it arrives at the Site or after it leaves the Site. 

### About the Policy

This privacy policy is effective October 23, 2009. If we change this Policy, we will post the amended Policy on the Site so that you are aware of what User Information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time, so please review the Site frequently for any changes. Amendments to this Policy will be posted on the Site and will be effective when posted. You will be deemed to have been made aware of, will be subject to, and will be deemed to have accepted, the changes to any amended or revised Policy by your continued use of our services or the Site. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, or by email or by notice posted on our website. 

If you have questions specifically about this Policy, or to legal issues pertaining to the practices of the Site or your use of the Site, please contact us. 

Due to the high volume of inquiries we receive, we regret that we cannot respond to individual inquiries asking for information about specific jobs, companies, how to apply to jobs and companies, education programs, schools, or how to apply to education programs and schools except as represented in the Site. 

### Contact Information

  * Electronic: 
  * To opt out of e-mail communications email us at: optout@getthejob.com 
  * To cancel or correct your personal information: send an email with your User Name and the notice "My User Information" in the subject line to myinfo@getthejob.com 
  * To express or ask questions regarding privacy concerns: send an email to feedback@getthejob.com 

  * General contact info for Getthejob.com: 
  * Main phone: 781-683-3300 
  * Mailing address: 10 Presidential Way Woburn, MA 01801
